Paul Baran Papers M1817
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Com21 Date:010901 (Container 73, Folder 24)
  Access Business Com21
- Com21 Date:010903 (Container 73, Folder 25)
- Com21 Date:010910 (Container 73, Folder 27)
  Product Revenue/Cost Trend
- Com21 Date:011003 (Container 73, Folder 29)
  Conan Review
- Com21 Date:011008 (Container 73, Folder 30)
  A New Concept - the Virtual PVR Set Top
- Com21 Date:011015 (Container 73, Folder 31)
  Board Presentation Materials
- Com21 Date:011016 (Container 73, Folder 33)
  Financial Models
- Com21 Date:011016 (Container 73, Folder 34)
  Question from jcpoint regarding DOCSIS; answered by Dave
- Com21 Date:011019 (Container 73, Folder 35)
  AOL to Show Up on '2000' Boxes
- Com21 Date:011120 (Container 73, Folder 36)
  Signature Required for S-8 Filing (Brobeck)
- Com21 Date:011022 (Container 73, Folder 37)
  Key Facts & Figures on Com21; Working Paper #2, Recent Related Activities by CableLabs
- Com21 Date:011022 (Container 73, Folder 38)
  CT's Pipeline, "Some Have Won One-Dot-One -- Now What?"
- Com21 Date:011031 (Container 73, Folder 39)
  Strategy, Tactics, Organization, Key Contributors, Recommendations
- Com21 Date:011116 (Container 73, Folder 40)
  Set-top Project - Status and Next Steps
- Com21 Date:011231 (Container 73, Folder 41)
  Annual Report, 2001; Stockholder Annual Meeting, May 16, 2002; SEC Form 10-K
- Com21 Date:020101 (Container 73, Folder 42)
  PB signature required by SEC
- Com21 Date:020327 (Container 73, Folder 43)
  Revised Com21 10-K
- Com21 Date:020402 (Container 73, Folder 44)
  Audit Committee Consent
- PB Chronological Scrapbook (Container 74)
- PB Papers 1950-1966 box 2 (Container 75)
  Previous box is 171
- Com21 Date:900131 (Container 76, Folder 1)
  FCC regarding Metricom (FCC prior to 1992)
- Com21 Date:910611 (Container 76, Folder 2)
  AltCom - Vol. 1: Business Plan
- Com21 Date:911018 (Container 76, Folder 3)
  AltCom - Briefing (preliminary discussion draft)
- Com21 Date:911021 (Container 76, Folder 4)
  AltCom - AT&T and GTE discussions
- Com21 Date:911125 (Container 76, Folder 5)
  The Com21 Group Business Plan (preliminary discussion draft)
- Com21 Date:930115 (Container 76, Folder 6)
  Texas Instruments, Inc. Discussions
- Com21 Date:930923 (Container 76, Folder 7)
  FCC: Notice of Proposed Rule Making
- Com21 Date:931108 (Container 76, Folder 8)
  Rules for the narrowband decision (made in July)
- Com21 Date:950315 (Container 76, Folder 9)
  White Paper for NAS CPS Spring Conference on N11
- Com21 Date:960401 (Container 76, Folder 10)
  An Assessment of Telecommunications Act of 1996 & Impact on Converging Communications,etc
- Com21 Date:960419 (Container 76, Folder 11)
- PB Papers 1967-1969 box 1 (Container 77)
- Com21 Date:930106 (Container 81, Folder 1)
  Slides: The Concept, How We Do It, Applications, Where We Differ, etc.
- Com21 Date:930211 (Container 81, Folder 2)
  Time-Warner Full Service Network
- Com21 Date:930412 (Container 81, Folder 3)
  Texas Instruments; Time Warner
- Com21 Date:940417 (Container 81, Folder 4)
  Progress Report
- Com21 Date:950122 (Container 81, Folder 5)
  EDS
- Com21 Date:950726 (Container 81, Folder 6)
  Board Meeting, July 26, 1995
- Com21 Date:950115 (Container 81, Folder 7)
  Presentation: "Communications for the 21st Century"
- Com21 Date:000101 (Container 81, Folder 8)
  Individual Office Layout
- Com21 Date:000101 (Container 81, Folder 9)
  SPECS - "CableLabs Certifies Modem from DX Antenna Co.
- Com21 Date:000408 (Container 81, Folder 10)
  Computer Telephony (Michael)
- Com21 Date:000413 (Container 81, Folder 11)
  Quarter 1 - Results
- Com21 Date:000416 (Container 81, Folder 12)
  Quarter 2 - Clipping Report
- Com21 Date:000501 (Container 81, Folder 13)
  Roundtable Meeting
- Com21 Date:000506 (Container 81, Folder 14)
- Com21 Date:000601 (Container 81, Folder 15)
  Quarter 3 - Clipping Report
- Com21 Date:000615 (Container 81, Folder 16)
  Merchant & Gould - Withdrawal of William Cochran
- Com21 Date:000630 (Container 81, Folder 17)
  First European Board of Advisors Meeting, June 30, 2000
- Com21 Date:000705 (Container 81, Folder 18)
  Focus on Cable vs. Divert Resources to Wireless
- Com21 Date:000717 (Container 81, Folder 19)
  FAQ about Customer Owned Dark Fiber
- Com21 Date:000816 (Container 81, Folder 20)
  Excite News: "Com 21 Appoints Sales & Marketing Executives (Mishell and Koepsel)
- Com21 Date:000817 (Container 81, Folder 21)
  Cees Witvliet and Some Topics for the Next US-BoA Meeting
- Com21 Date:000818 (Container 81, Folder 22)
  Constant Need to Re-Provision (re: IP provisioning problem)
- Com21 Date:000901 (Container 81, Folder 23)
  The Open Door, "Com21 Modem Sales Benefit Local Communities"
- Com21 Date:000910 (Container 81, Folder 24)
  Comments on Com21 (James Spilker)
- Com21 Date:000918 (Container 81, Folder 25)
  David Brown, Newly Hired Director of Product Planning
- Com21 Date:000920 (Container 81, Folder 26)
  Deutsche Banc Alex. Brown
- Com21 Date:000920 (Container 81, Folder 27)
  Access Business Unit - Sunil Frida, Senior Product Manager
- Com21 Date:000920 (Container 81, Folder 28)
  Board of Directors Meeting, Sept. 20,2000
- Com21 Date:000920 (Container 81, Folder 29)
  Board of Advisors Meeting, Sept. 20-21, 2000
- Com21 Date:001004 (Container 81, Folder 30)
  Com21 Pres. & CEO Joins BiTMICRO Networks Board
- Com21 Date:001011 (Container 81, Folder 31)
  Quarter 4 - Clipping Reports
- Com21 Date:010323 (Container 81, Folder 32)
  Securities & Exchange Commission Form 10-K Annual Report
- Com21 Date:001030 (Container 81, Folder 33)
  A "Block-MPEG" PHY offering Adaptive Modulation and Coding
- Com21 Date:001101 (Container 81, Folder 34)
  Wireless Company (WCO), Michael Gordon
- Com21 Date:001101 (Container 81, Folder 35)
  Wireless Company (WCO), John Langley
- Com21 Date:001113 (Container 81, Folder 36)
  Excite News: "High-Capacity Multiple Service Extends Cisco's Leadership in the Cable Industry"
- Com21 Date:001114 (Container 81, Folder 37)
  Gilder Technology Report: "Terayon Expands Focus"
- Com21 Date:001201 (Container 81, Folder 38)
  EETimes - Free Subscription Form
- Com21 Date:001211 (Container 81, Folder 39)
  Memo to High Speed Data Customers - Info on transitioning to AT&T@Home
- Com21 Date:001204 (Container 81, Folder 40)
  Memo from Spilker re: Meeting Friday to discuss Plan for Profitability, Wireless strategy, Israeli Division
- Com21 Date:001230 (Container 81, Folder 41)
  Marshall capital Management
- PB Files 4073-4074 (Container 82)
  Awards
- Com21 Date:970519 (Container 85, Folder 1)
  Internet Telephony (FitzGerald)
- Com21 Date:970519 (Container 85, Folder 2)
  Broadband Week, "Com21 Locks Fifth Cable-Modem Trial"
- Com21 Date:990601 (Container 85, Folder 3)
  Com21 Planning Meeting
- Com21 Date:990127 (Container 85, Folder 4)
  U.S. Provisional Patent App. for Elimination of Ingress Noise in Cable Systems Using Tandem Grounded Common Mode Filter
- Com21 Date:010125 (Container 85, Folder 5)
  CEDaily Direct, "Broadcom Blazes a Trail"
- Com21 Date:990530 (Container 85, Folder 6)
  Comments on Tech. Ability to Implement Open access Provisioning via High-Speed Data etc
- Com21 Date:000202 (Container 85, Folder 7)
  PB Bio for Proxy
- Com21 Date:000206 (Container 85, Folder 8)
  Com21 Product Information; "Gauging the Real Hacker Threat to Your Network", "GIGABIT Ethernet Over Copper"
- Com21 Date:000223 (Container 85, Folder 9)
  U.S. Patent App."Method & Apparatus for an Application Interface module in a Subscriber Terminal Unit"
- Com21 Date:000306 (Container 85, Folder 10)
  Action by Unanimous Written Consent of the Board" (resolution of Robert Hoff)
- Com21 Date:000313 (Container 85, Folder 11)
  Board Preparation for March 28 Meeting
- Com21 Date:000324 (Container 85, Folder 12)
  8 folders on Com21's growth, long-range strategy, vision, acquisition, and hiring
- Com21 Date:000328 (Container 85, Folder 13)
  Advisory Board Meeting
- Com21 Date:000400 (Container 85, Folder 14)
  Broadband Wireless, "Broadband Wireless Access Update"
- Com21 Date:000414 (Container 85, Folder 15)
  Preferred Capital Markets (Com21); Terayon Communications Systems
- Com21 Date:000427 (Container 85, Folder 16)
  TechWeb, "Data Communications"
- Com21 Date:000500 (Container 85, Folder 17)
  DVB, "Guidelines for use of Specification DVB Interaction Channel for Cable TV Distribution Systems"
- Com21 Date:000522 (Container 85, Folder 18)
  Large folder with 3 folders on Terayon (Market Guide, ProVestor Plus Company Report, Valuations, etc)
- Com21 Date:000525 (Container 85, Folder 19)
  Audit Committee Presentation, May 25, 2000
- Com21 Date:000530 (Container 85, Folder 20)
  Morgan Stanley Dean Witter: "Broadband Communications: Cable TV - The Time to Buy Selectively"
- Com21 Date:000601 (Container 85, Folder 21)
  Application for U.S. Non-Provisional Utility Patent
- Com21 Date:000601 (Container 85, Folder 22)
  Industry News - View on Europe
- Com21 Date:000707 (Container 85, Folder 23)
  SEC - Signature Request
- Com21 Date:000920 (Container 85, Folder 24)
  Project Coolidge - Presentation to Board of Directors
- Com21 Date:000920 (Container 85, Folder 25)
  Credit Suisse/First Boston: Project Coolidge
- Com21 Date:000928 (Container 85, Folder 26)
  Distribution of Materials for Board Meeting, Sept. 28 (PB comments on Terayon)
- Com21 Date:980101 (Container 87, Folder 1)
  Bound Volume: Hybrid 1997-8, Reading Books
- Com21 Date:010930 (Container 87, Folder 2)
  Bound Volume: Conan Project
- Com21 Date:011001 (Container 87, Folder 3)
  Bound Volume: Conan Estimates
- Com21 Date:021020 (Container 87, Folder 5)
  Bound Volume: Microsoft Interaction
- PB Patents (Container 88)
- Com21 Date:780407 (Container 89, Folder 1)
  U. S. Patent: "Multiple Access Digital Communications System"
- Com21 Date:910401 (Container 89, Folder 2)
  The Never-Ending Story: Telephone Company Anticompetitive Behavior Since the Breakup of AT&T
- Com21 Date:930728 (Container 89, Folder 3)
  U. S. Patent: "Remote Link Adapter for Use in TV Broadcast Data Transmission System"
- Com21 Date:931129 (Container 89, Folder 4)
  Accel Partners; Com21 First Advisory Board Meeting, etc.
- Com21 Date:940415 (Container 89, Folder 5)
  NDA Forms - Proprietary Information Agreement
- Com21 Date:940603 (Container 89, Folder 6)
  Mark Laubach (resume)
- Com21 Date:940630 (Container 89, Folder 7)
  Balance Sheet as of June 30, 1994
- Com21 Date:940815 (Container 89, Folder 8)
  Charlie Williams - StrataCom
- Com21 Date:940829 (Container 89, Folder 9)
  Dale Hatfield's letter to Mike Bowles re: Jim Chiddix
- Com21 Date:940905 (Container 89, Folder 10)
  Conversations with Howell, Beard, Spaduzzi, Barton
- Com21 Date:941209 (Container 89, Folder 11)
  Com21 Progress Report #6, Nov. 1994
- Com21 Date:950109 (Container 89, Folder 12)
  Com21 Progress Report #7, Dec. 1994
- Com21 Date:950208 (Container 89, Folder 13)
  Com21 Progress Report #8, Jan. 1995
- Com21 Date:950615 (Container 89, Folder 14)
  Cable Box Internet
- Com21 Date:951202 (Container 89, Folder 15)
  P3 Project Engineering
- Com21 Date:960101 (Container 89, Folder 16)
  Morrison & Foerster: Executive Summary of the Telecommunications Act of 1996
- Com21 Date:960424 (Container 89, Folder 17)
  MCNS Data over Cable Project
- Com21 Date:960508 (Container 89, Folder 18)
  Com21 Quarterly News & Highlights
- Com21 Date:011008 (Container 89, Folder 19)
  Conan Project
- Com21 Date:011019 (Container 89, Folder 20)
  Cablelabs DOCSIS Set-top Gateway (DSG) Interface Specification
- Com21 Date:020731 (Container 89, Folder 21)
  Information on Com21 Prepared by Investec
- Com21 Date:940623 (Container 91, Folder 1)
  Scott Laubach's Notes from 4th International ATM/B-ISDN Workshop
- Com21 Date:950509 (Container 91, Folder 2)
  Sharp Tuner for Digital CATV
- Com21 Date:950609 (Container 91, Folder 3)
  QAMLinktm Quotation
- Com21 Date:950816 (Container 91, Folder 4)
  The Effect of Internal Impairments on Performance of P2Modem, Sabin
- Com21 Date:950928 (Container 91, Folder 5)
  Mongoose ASIC Functional Specification
- Com21 Date:960226 (Container 91, Folder 6)
  P3 RF STU Tuner Performance Comparison Data
- Com21 Date:960422 (Container 91, Folder 7)
  Telephony Functional Specification
- Com21 Date:980501 (Container 91, Folder 8)
  Reserved Share Information - Board of Directors Allotments
- Com21 Date:980501 (Container 91, Folder 9)
  Employee Stock Purchase Plan
- Com21 Date:980723 (Container 91, Folder 10)
  Acknowledgment page to Com21 Insider Trading Policy
- Com21 Date:000202 (Container 91, Folder 11)
  16 folders (grouped by PB) on Terayon
- Com21 Date:000309 (Container 91, Folder 12)
  SEC Commission - Form 10-K
- Com21 Date:000406 (Container 91, Folder 13)
  Board of Directors Meeting, April 6, 2002
- Com21 (Container 94)
  Board stuff & MSC
- Com21 Date:010401 (Container 95, Folder 1)
  Bound Clipping Reports, Quarter 1
- Com21 Date:010418 (Container 95, Folder 2)
  Board of Directors Meeting materials, April 18, 2001
- Com21 Date:010618 (Container 95, Folder 3)
  Agenda, Board Meeting June 18, 2001
- Com21 Date:010618 (Container 95, Folder 4)
  CEO Stock Options; Access Products Divisions Update; Board Meeting, June 18, 2001
- Com21 Date:010718 (Container 95, Folder 5)
  Board of Directors Meeting materials, July 18, 2001
- Com21 Date:010901 (Container 95, Folder 6)
  Bound Clipping Reports, Quarter 3
- Com21 Date:011017 (Container 95, Folder 8)
  Board of Directors Meeting materials, Oct. 17, 2001
- Com21 Date:011017 (Container 95, Folder 9)
  Board of Directors Meeting - Business Update, Oct. 17, 2001
- Com21 Date:011028 (Container 95, Folder 10)
  Memo from Charles Cheevers, Com21 Goals, etc.
- Com21 Date:011018 (Container 95, Folder 11)
  Investor Conference Call, Oct. 18, 2001
- Com21 Date:011018 (Container 95, Folder 12)
  Press Release: "Com21 Achieves $30.1 Million in 3rd Quarter Revenue"
- Com21 Date:011120 (Container 95, Folder 13)
  Silicon Valley Bank Loan & Security Agreement
- Com21 Date:011128 (Container 95, Folder 14)
  Silicon Valley Bank Resolution
- Com21 Date:020211 (Container 95, Folder 15)
  Multichannel News - Broadband articles
- Com21 Date:020213 (Container 95, Folder 16)
  DOCSIS MAC PDU Efficiency: European Design Centre, Cork, Ireland
- Com21 Date:020219 (Container 95, Folder 17)
  The Retrovue Head End (Betelgeuse) -- a Preliminary Description (PB)
- Com21 Date:020501 (Container 95, Folder 18)
  Ballmer's Talk to National Cable TV Asso; Perception of Microsoft ITV
- Com21 Date:020603 (Container 95, Folder 19)
  Q & A with Moshe Lichtman
- Com21 Date:021001 (Container 95, Folder 21)
  Juniper Networks Delivers Highest Performing Compact
- Com21 Date:021016 (Container 95, Folder 22)
  Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, Oct. 16, 2002
- Com21 Date:021027 (Container 95, Folder 23)
  Com21's Status (PB)
- Com21 Date:021127 (Container 95, Folder 24)
  Com21's SEC Filing (names)
- Com21 Date:021231 (Container 95, Folder 26)
  SEC Form 10-K - Com21
- Com21 Date:030122 (Container 95, Folder 27)
  Board of Directors Meeting, Jan.22, 2003
- Com21 Date:030210 (Container 95, Folder 28)
  Questionnaire for Directors, Officers, & Principal Stockholders
- Com21 Date:030217 (Container 95, Folder 29)
  Bonus Proposal (from Spilker)
- Com 21 Date:940524 (Container 96, Folder 1)
  Stock Distribution, Shareholders Consent, and other stock matters (3 folders)
- Com 21 Date:970826 (Container 96, Folder 2)
  Waiver & Amendment of Right of First Refusal
- Com 21 Date:971110 (Container 96, Folder 3)
  IPO, Prospectus, Standoff Agreement, etc (5 folders)
- Com 21 Date:980325 (Container 96, Folder 4)
  Com21 - Initial Public Offering
- Com 21 Date:980417 (Container 96, Folder 5)
  IPO Slides, Prospectus, "Red Herring", etc. (5 folders)
- Com 21 Date:981112 (Container 96, Folder 6)
  Advisory Board Meetings (6 folders)
- Com 21 Date:990703 (Container 96, Folder 7)
  Hybrid Networks - Class Action; U. S. District Court, San Jose Division
- Com 21 Date:991217 (Container 96, Folder 8)
  Board Meeting and Attachments, Dec. 17, 1999
- Com 21 Date:000106 (Container 96, Folder 9)
  Board Meeting and Attachments, Jan. 12, 2000
- Com21 Date:970101 (Container 97, Folder 1)
  Five folders, Board Meetings
- Com21 Date:980101 (Container 97, Folder 2)
  Clippings, Annual Reports, Presentations, etc.
- Com21 Date:990101 (Container 97, Folder 3)
  Discussions, Mergers, Offerings, etc.
- Com21 Date:940810 (Container 98, Folder 1)
  Draft of Minutes, August 10, 1994, from Heller Ehrman
- Com21 Date:940920 (Container 98, Folder 2)
  Sept. Board Meeting (agenda, etc)
- Com21 Date:941017 (Container 98, Folder 3)
  Oct. 15 Advisory Board Meeting Follow-up
- Com21 Date:941027 (Container 98, Folder 4)
  Draft of Board Minutes, Oct. 25, 1994, from Heller Ehrman
- Com21 Date:941214 (Container 98, Folder 5)
  Series A Preferred Stockholders of Com21 - Stockholder consent
- Com21 Date:950208 (Container 98, Folder 6)
  Feb. 8 Board Meeting (agenda, etc)
- Com21 Date:950515 (Container 98, Folder 7)
  Invitation to PB from Annenberg Public policy Center to participate in seminar (Oct. 13)
- Com21 Date:950726 (Container 98, Folder 8)
  Draft of Board Minutes, July 26, 1995
- Com21 Date:950814 (Container 98, Folder 9)
  Board Minutes and attachments, August 14, 1995
- Com21 Date:950907 (Container 98, Folder 10)
  Board Minutes and attachments, Sept. 7, 1995
- Com21 Date:951006 (Container 98, Folder 11)
  Board Minutes and attachments, Oct. 6, 1995
- Com21 Date:951120 (Container 98, Folder 12)
  Board Minutes and attachments, Nov. 20, 1995
- Com21 Date:960115 (Container 98, Folder 13)
  Board Minutes and attachments, Jan. 15, 1996
- Com21 Date:960207 (Container 98, Folder 14)
  Board Minutes and attachments, Feb. 7, 1996
- Com21 Date:960418 (Container 98, Folder 15)
  Board Minutes and attachments, April 22, 1996
- Com21 Date:960515 (Container 98, Folder 16)
  Board Minutes and attachments, May 20, 1996
- Com21 Date:960620 (Container 98, Folder 17)
  Board Minutes and attachments, June 25, 1996
- Com21 Date:960726 (Container 98, Folder 18)
  Board Minutes and attachments, July 30, 1996 - and corrections
- Com21 Date:960819 (Container 98, Folder 19)
  Board Minutes and attachments, Aug. 22, 1996
- Com21 Date:960926 (Container 98, Folder 20)
  Board Minutes and attachments, Sept. 26, 1996
- Com21 Date:961031 (Container 98, Folder 21)
  Board Minutes and attachments, Oct. 31, 1996
- Com21 Date:961119 (Container 98, Folder 22)
  Board Minutes and attachments, Nov. 21, 1996
- Com21 Date:961216 (Container 98, Folder 23)
  Board Minutes and attachments, Dec. 18, 1996
- Com21 Date:970128 (Container 98, Folder 24)
  Board Minutes and attachments, Jan. 30, 1997
- Com21 Date:970218 (Container 98, Folder 25)
  Board Minutes and attachments, Feb. 20, 1997
- Com21 Date:970324 (Container 98, Folder 26)
  Board Minutes and attachments, March 26, 1997
- Com21 Date:970327 (Container 98, Folder 27)
  Revised Board Meeting schedules, through 1997
- Com21 Date:970523 (Container 98, Folder 28)
  Board Minutes and attachments, May 29, 1997
- Com21 Date:950908 (Container 99, Folder 1)
  Com21 Board Meetings - 5 Folders
- Com21 Date:000818 (Container 99, Folder 2)
  Background Information - Evaluating Com21's Strengths and Weaknesses (PB)
- Com21 Date:000828 (Container 99, Folder 3)
  Excite - Money & Investing
- Com21 Date:000903 (Container 99, Folder 4)
  New Co. Inc, Financial Structure
- Com21 Date:000906 (Container 99, Folder 5)
  Com21 Broadband Solutions, Craig Soderquist, Sr. VP
- Com21 Date:011027 (Container 99, Folder 6)
  Com21 P&L; July 2001 Grants
- Com21 Date:011217 (Container 99, Folder 7)
  Agenda, Dec. 17, 2001
- Com21 Date:020113 (Container 99, Folder 8)
  Board Meeting, Jan. 16, 2002 - Agenda, Minutes previous meeting; Quarter 4th Report
- Com21 Date:020115 (Container 99, Folder 9)
  Board of Advisors Meeting, Jan. 15, 2002
- Com21 Date:020221 (Container 99, Folder 10)
  Brobeck, Phleger & Harrison, copy of Audit Committee Questionnaire
- Com21 Date:020417 (Container 99, Folder 11)
  Board Meeting, April 17, 2002; Quarter 1 Report; Jan. 16 Minutes
- Com21 Date:020520 (Container 99, Folder 12)
  Stockholder Rights Plans; Baker & McKenzie Securities Practice Group Meeting
- Com21 Date:020530 (Container 99, Folder 13)
  Board of Directors Meeting, May 30, 2002
- Com21 Date:020530 (Container 99, Folder 14)
  Minutes of Special Meeting of Board, May 30, 2002; Quarter 2 Audit Committee; Rights Agreement
- Com21 Date:020812 (Container 99, Folder 15)
  Adoption of Stockholder Rights Plans
- Com21 Date:021005 (Container 99, Folder 16)
  National Academy of Engineering (NAE) Annual Meeting, Oct. 7, 2002, Washington
- Com21 Date:021016 (Container 99, Folder 17)
  Quarter 3, Audit Committee Meeting; Board Report, October 2002
- Scrapbook Stuff (Container 100)
  Box 2 of 3
- Publications & Misc 4200-4292 (Container 101)
  Box 1 of 2
- Publications & Misc 4200-4292 (Container 102)
  Box 2 of 2
- Com21/Altcom Date:910715 (Container 104, Folder 2)
  Altcom Reading Book, Original Vol. 1, Business Issues
- Com21/Altcom Date:910715 (Container 104, Folder 3)
  Altcom Reading Book, Original Vol. 2, Transmission
- Com21/Altcom Date:910715 (Container 104, Folder 4)
  Altcom Reading Book, Original Vol. 3, Switching & Tech
- Com21/Altcom Date:920402 (Container 104, Folder 5)
  The Com21 Group: Business Overview
- Com21/Altcom Date:920402 (Container 104, Folder 6)
  Com21: Financial Model
- Com21/Altcom Date:920725 (Container 104, Folder 7)
  The Com21 System Business Plan
- Com21/Altcom Date:930121 (Container 104, Folder 8)
  The Com21 System - Business Plan Update
- Com21/Altcom Date:930301 (Container 104, Folder 9)
  The Com21 - Business Plan
- Com21 Date:930227 (Container 105, Folder 1)
  Charles Wohlstetter Meeting, Feb. 26, 1993
- Com21 Date:930524 (Container 105, Folder 2)
  Memo from Bill Houser; memos, request for Business Plan, etc.
- Com21 Date:940805 (Container 105, Folder 3)
  Progress Report #2 - July, 1994
- Com21 Date:940912 (Container 105, Folder 4)
  Hybrid Information (10 folders)
- Com21 Date:940923 (Container 105, Folder 5)
  Advisory Board Meeting and Open House
- Com21 Date:941102 (Container 105, Folder 6)
  Employee phone numbers; Conversation notes from Nick Hamilton-Piercy, Rogers Cable
- Com21 Date:941107 (Container 105, Folder 7)
  Progress Report #5 - October, 1994
- Com21 Date:941116 (Container 105, Folder 8)
  Patent Application - "Remote Link Adapter for Use in TV Broadcast Data Transmission"
- Com21 Date:950601 (Container 105, Folder 9)
  Letter from Keith Kasue of Penrod
- Com21 Date:951201 (Container 105, Folder 10)
  Corporate Backgrounder, Fourth Quarter, 1995
- Com21 Date:960101 (Container 105, Folder 11)
  Com21 PB Presentation - Microdax
- Com21 Date:960522 (Container 105, Folder 12)
  Slides INB, Smart Filter
- Com21 Date:960616 (Container 105, Folder 13)
  Business in China - from Penrod International
- Com21 Date:960822 (Container 105, Folder 14)
  Apparatus and Method for Extending the Range of universal Serial Bus Operations (PB)
- Com21 Date:961217 (Container 105, Folder 15)
  U.S. Patent: Adaptive Electronic Filter
- Com21 Date:970504 (Container 105, Folder 16)
  Terayon's Analysis of S-CMDA
- Com21 Date:970608 (Container 105, Folder 17)
  COM21 comUNITYSystem and Cornerstone Voice Interoperability Test Report
- Com21 Date:970728 (Container 105, Folder 18)
  Telephone System Architecture
- Com21 Date:970801 (Container 105, Folder 19)
  ComUNITYaccess system sales manual, August 1977 Update
- Com21 Date:970901 (Container 105, Folder 20)
  ComUNITYaccess system sales manual, Sept. 1977 Update
- Com21 Date:971001 (Container 105, Folder 21)
  ComUNITYaccess system sales manual, Oct. 1977 Update
- Com21 Date:971101 (Container 105, Folder 22)
  ComUNITYaccess system sales manual, Nov. 1977 Update
- Com21 Date:971201 (Container 105, Folder 23)